<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SimpleNewDownloader-29March</string>

    <string name="hOne">🚀 Viral Hits of the Week</string>
    <string name="bOne">Discover the internet’s most talked-about videos right now! Our algorithm tracks viral trends across social media, bringing you everything from hilarious fails and heartwarming moments to jaw-dropping stunts and global challenges. Whether it’s a TikTok dance craze, a YouTube short gone viral, or a Reel that’s breaking the internet, you’ll find it here first. Updated hourly so you never miss what’s trending—watch, share, and join the conversation!</string>

    <string name="hTwo">🎬 Top Trending Movies &amp; Trailers</string>
    <string name="bTwo">Dive into the cinematic buzz with the most-watched trailers, behind-the-scenes clips, and iconic movie moments dominating conversations worldwide. From Hollywood blockbusters to indie gems gaining sudden fame, this section is your front-row seat to film culture. Watch exclusive sneak peeks, fan-edited supercuts, and viral scenes from classics resurfacing. Perfect for film buffs who want to stay ahead of the next big release or rediscover forgotten favorites now trending again.</string>

    <string name="hThree">🎵 Music Videos Blowing Up</string>
    <string name="bThree">Feel the beat of what’s hot in music! This section showcases viral music videos, breakout artist performances, and underground tracks exploding in popularity. Whether it’s a K-pop dance routine, a hip-hop freestyle, or a nostalgic throwback track making a comeback, you’ll experience it here in crystal-clear quality. Discover new genres, trending lyrics, and fan-made edits that are reshaping the charts. Press play and ride the wave of today’s musical zeitgeist!</string>

    <string name="hFour">📢 News &amp; Trending Clips</string>
    <string name="bFour">Stay informed in minutes with bite-sized news clips that are shaping global conversations. From breaking political updates and scientific breakthroughs to viral social justice moments and quirky local stories, we curate the most impactful videos you need to see. Summarized for clarity and context, these clips cut through the noise—perfect for busy viewers who want to stay updated without sifting through hours of coverage. Knowledge is power, and here, it’s delivered at lightning speed.</string>

    <string name="hFive">😂 Memes &amp; Comedy Gold</string>
    <string name="bFive">Laughter guaranteed! This section is packed with the internet’s freshest memes, pranks, stand-up clips, and absurdly funny sketches that have millions sharing and rewatching. From relatable everyday humor to surreal edits that defy explanation, these videos are mood-boosters curated to make your day brighter. Updated constantly to reflect the fastest-moving comedy trends, so you’ll always be in on the joke. Warning: side effects may include uncontrollable giggles and the urge to spam your group chats.</string>


</resources>